<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PawPatrol</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="profile">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_services">Services</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Logout</string>

    <!-- Terms content -->
    <string name="terms_content">
    By using our dog-walking services, you agree to the following terms and conditions:\n\n
    1. Service Agreement: We will provide dog-walking services as requested, based on availability and in accordance with the scheduled time.\n\n
    2. User Responsibilities: You are responsible for ensuring that your dog is healthy, vaccinated, and fit for walking. We are not liable for any injuries to your pet during the walking sessions.\n\n
    3. Payment: Payments for services must be made before or upon completion of the scheduled walk. Prices are subject to change, and you will be notified in advance.\n\n
    4. Cancellations: If you wish to cancel or reschedule a booking, please do so at least 24 hours in advance. Cancellations made within 24 hours of the scheduled time will incur a cancellation fee.\n\n
    5. Liability: We are not liable for any damages or injuries caused during the service, including to your pet or any third parties.\n\n
    6. Privacy: Your personal information will be used solely for the purpose of providing the requested services and will not be shared with any third parties without your consent.\n\n
    7. Changes to Terms: We reserve the right to update these terms at any time. Changes will be communicated to you through the app.
</string>

    <!-- FAQs content -->
    <string name="faqs_content">
        Here you can find answers to common questions about our dog-walking services.\n\n
        1. What is the service provided? \n
        We offer professional dog-walking services for all types of dogs. We ensure the safety and well-being of your pet during each walk.\n\n
        2. How do I book a walk for my dog? \n
        You can book a walk using our mobile app or website. Simply select the date, time, and your preferred walker.\n\n
        3. What if I need to cancel or reschedule a walk? \n
        Cancellations can be made at least 24 hours in advance to avoid any fees. Rescheduling is also available.\n\n
        4. How do I pay for the service? \n
        Payment can be made online via credit card or through our app, prior to the scheduled walk.\n\n
        5. Are your walkers experienced? \n
        Yes, all of our walkers are experienced in handling dogs of all breeds and sizes, and are trained in pet safety.\n\n
        6. Is there an age limit for dogs to be walked? \n
        We accept dogs of all ages, but puppies and elderly dogs may have specific walking requirements.\n\n
        If you have any more questions, feel free to contact us directly!
    </string>

</resources>